

Tel.: +44 7491274792 - Email: dmitryfakanov@gmail.com

PERSONAL STATEMENT

Working for several years in luxury retail I gained relevant experience at the highest levels of customer service. I also gained experience in e-commerce, logistics and purchasing.

I have a strong interest in Software development. I have finished a Boot camp with JustIT as well as a few other professional courses in Software development. I gained skills in Front End and Back End Software development. I studied HTML5, CSS, JavaScript with React for the Front End and Python, databases for the Back End Software development.

EDUCATION

LD COMITOR	
10/2023 - 01/24	Bootcamp Just IT, Software development. Covered: development of HTML, JavaScript and CSS. Understanding basic methodologies for using HTML & JavaScript; Structure, Layout, coding; Use of CSS within a web-based product. Database design (MySQL & MongoDB). Understanding the importance of linking software to database; key features of databases and data stores; creating database. Python development. You may see my portfolio below: https://dimiuk.github.io/project-portfolio/
09/2023 - 03/24	Professional Course Robot_dreams IT school, Python Development.
	Covered: GitHub and Terminal; Python's main libraries and frameworks; object-oriented programming; code testing – unit, integration, end-to-end testing; working with data bases, SQL; working with Flask, Django, Docker; APIs; network programming – HTML, CSS, JS, APIs.
06/2023 - 07/23	Professional Course City Lit, London, Microsoft Excel. Covered: working with
	main formulas such as Sumif, Countif, Vlookup, Hlookup and others; working with Pivot Tables; advanced filtering; conditional formatting; recording macros.
10/2022 - 12/22	Professional Course General Assembly London, JavaScript Development.
	Covered: JavaScript (ES6) and object-oriented programming; hands on experience with APIs and React, JavaScript and jQuery, the browser, and the DOM.
02/2022 - 04/22	Professional Course General Assembly London, Front-End Web Development. Covered: JavaScript (arrays and loops, objects, functions); CSS (responsive design, UI components) and HTML; DOM elements manipulation with JavaScript; APIs implementation; GitHub experience. Project website created https://dimiuk.github.io/myProject/
11/2021 - 12/21	Professional Course London College of Fashion, Buying and Merchandising for
	Online Retail.
04/2020 - 06/20	Professional Online Course Google Digital Garage, Digital Marketing.
02/2020 - 03/20	Professional Course London College of Fashion, Fashion Buying and Merchandising.
09/2018 - 07/19	PGC Birkbeck University of London, Postgraduate degree in Business
	Innovation.
09/2017 - 11/17	Professional Course City Lit, London, Advanced digital marketing.
09/2005 - 08/06	MSc The Prydniprovska State Academy of Civil Engineering & Architecture, Qualification; Specialist of International Economics.
09/2001 - 08/05	BA The Prydniprovska State Academy of Civil Engineering & Architecture, Qualification; Specialist of International Economics.

SELECTED WORK EXPERIENCE

08/2022 - 11/2023 Louis Vuitton, Harrods Client Advisor

Achieved: Achieved: Enhanced individual and team objectives and sales.

Provided best Client experience and developed long-term relationships by leveraging different clientele tools, in order to foster Brand loyalty. Performed as a team-player, participated in all activities contributing to the overall objectives of the store. Learnt and mastered Brand and product knowledge.

05/2018 - 01/2022 Gucci Ltd, Harrods Client Advisor

Achieved: Awarded twice highest level of costumer' satisfaction *Ambassador* by the Gucci and Harrods mystery shopper programme.

Provided customers with top quality service, fully met and exceeded their needs and expectations as well as increased the brand loyalty; Collaborated with buying team providing reports for different collections resulting in maximised sales; Coached new starters staff managing them to optimise their new role and ease them into their new position so that they felt comfortable and effective in their new role; Fostered open and constructive communication with team members.

10/2017 - 03/2018 Harrods (Knightsbridge) Luxury department store Sales assistant

Achieved: Enhanced sales at the Burberry department store as well as Tom Ford, Zilli, Stefano Ricci, and Ralph Lauren brands.

Provided excellent customer service demonstrating exceptional product knowledge, and built quality customer relationships to achieve business goals. Other responsibilities included: Replenished the fitting and stock rooms and ensured a tidy stockroom; Worked as a part of a team by sharing selling support duties; Assisted with presentation of stock, ensuring that it followed the set standards.

01/2015 – 04/2016 Tile Expert Ltd. (Online trading with tiles) *E-commerce assistant* Achieved: Increased company's sales volume and broadened customer base by providing excellent customer support and service.

Communicated with suppliers of tiles requesting new catalogues and price lists; Built up on-line shop: uploaded new collections of tiles, photos, descriptions, prices and other related information onto the website; Pursued orders from customers to suppliers.

10/2011 – 07/2014 Silur Ltd. (Producing spare parts for agriculture equipment) *Purchase Assistant* Achieved: Harmonised the selling and buying procedures for a more effective use of resources.

Supervised the purchasing of all the necessary spare parts; Shortlisted manufacturers; Managed the timing of orders; Supervised product quality; Drafted the contracts and related documentation; Supervised delivery of orders.

04/2008 – 08/2011 Athena-Group Ltd. (Wholesale trading in consumer goods. Imports of a

OTHER SKILL AND PERSONAL INFORMATION

Experienced PC user: MS Office, Internet; Driving license holder.

LANGUAGES SPOKEN

Russian (mother tongue); Ukrainian (near native speaker); English (near native speaker); Italian (intermediate).

NATIONALITY: British and Ukrainian